DANISH PINJARI

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER



Jalgaon, Maharashtra, India 🖸 danishpinjari40@gmail.com

+91 9545445885

<u>danishpinjari</u> im

danishpinjari40

PROFILE

Front-end web developer with extensive experience in the MERN stack and various technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, as well as React.js. Likes to learn new technology. I am looking forward to making a meaningful contribution to a company through hard work.

PROJECTS

1.SILICONIX SHOP **LIVE** (7)





It's a react E-commerce web application with all the major functionalities Here you can buy any Electronic new Technology.

TECH STACK:

React | Redux | JavaScript | CSS3 | HTML5 | Chakra.UI | Rest.Api | JSON Server.

FEATURES:

- Homepage / Landing Page
- **Product Listing Page with Filters**
- **Product Description Page**
- Cart Management Page
- Wishlist Management Page
- Login / Logout Page
- Signup Page

Areas of responsibility:

- Add To Cart Page
- Add to Cart functionality
- · Adding And Removing functionality
- Wishlist Page
- Add to Cart functionality in Search page

2.URBAN COMPANY CLONE LIVE (7)





Through Urban Company, professionals with specific skills and experience can connect with those looking for those services. After a user joins the platform, our match-making algorithm identifies professionals who are available at the requested time and date that are closest to their requirements.

TECH STACK:

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | JSON server | FontAwesome | Local Storage

Landing Page | Home Page | Login/Signup | Shop | Cart | Checkout | Carousel

Areas of responsibility:

- An entire landing page including a footer and navbar.
- All product samples on the home page have hover effects.
- The home page features a carousel slide show.
- The Address Page map has been implemented using CSS.

EXPERIENCE

Bond Infotech, Jalgaon.

Front End Web Development, 03/2022 - 02/2023 | Full-Time | Internship.

Masai School, Bangalore. | Remote

Front End Web Development, 04/2022 - 10/2022 | Full-Time | Internship.

SKILLS AND FRAMEWORKS

- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- ES6
- BootStrap
- React. Js
- Redux
- Node. Js
- GitHub
- Chakra-UI

SOFT SKILL

- Team Collaboration
- Remote Work
- Time Management
- Problem-solving

EDUCATION

Masai School, Bangalore.

Front End Web Development, Full Time, 04/2022 - 10/2022. India

B.Tech (Mechanical Engineering)

Godavari College of Eng. August -2021 CGPA: 7.6 | completed.

M.J College, jalgaon / 2017 percentage: 55.08 % | Completed.

10 th

Igra Shahin High School, jalgaon / 2015 percentage: 77.20 % | Completed.